Guide to the Walter Gardner Hall Papers, 1923-1990 MS 280
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series II: The Democratic Party, 1944-1976
  - Subseries A: Party Politics, (1944-1973)
    - WGH - Fagan Dickson re Loyal Democrats of Texas - Creekmore Fath, Oct. - Dec. 1951 (Box 4, Folder 55)
    - Gilbert T. Adams to Byron Skelton re purpose of the Loyal Democrats, Nov. 1, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 56)
    - WGH to Honorable Allen Shivers re his support of the Democratic nominee in 1952, Nov. 14, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 57)
    - Charles Van Devander - Stuart Long re Wright Morrow; Loyal Democrats, Nov. 1951 (Box 4, Folder 58)
    - WGH to Democrats, Nov. 14, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 59)
    - WGH - Lillian Collier re San Jacinto River Authority, Dec. 10, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 60)
    - Fagan Dickson - WGH - letter of M.D. Warren, a Shelby County farmer, Dec. 6, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 61)
    - T.M. McCormick re labor unions, the left-wing and communists, Dec. 1951 (Box 4, Folder 62)
    - Loyal Democrats in the Panhandle of Texas, Dec. 1951 (Box 4, Folder 63)
    - WGH personal political expenses, Sept. 1951 - Nov. 1952 (Box 4, Folder 64)
    - Committee of 100 Texans (see also Series VI - Minnie Fisher Cunningham), Aug. 1951 - March 1952 (Box 4, Folder 65)
    - Loyal Democrats of Texas - Fagan Dickson - WGH, Jan. - March 1952 (Box 4, Folder 66)
    - WGH - National Democratic Committee, Jan. - March 1952 (Box 4, Folder 67)
    - WGH - Robert E. Ginna re the Republican Party compared to the Democrats, April 28, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 68)
    - WGH - John C. Granbery re candidates for the Senate from Texas, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 69)
    - WGH - Charlie Gibson - Loyal Democrats in the Texas Panhandle, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 70)
    - San Jacinto River Authority, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 71)
    - WGH - Jess R. Phillips, Jr. re Republican Party, June, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 72)
    - Democratic National Committee - India Edwards; Lawrence Westbrook, April - June 1952 (Box 4, Folder 73)
    - Loyal Democrats - Fagan Dickson; WGH, April - June 1952 (Box 4, Folder 74)
    - Harry Seay - WGH - Loyal Democrats in Dallas Co., April 1952 (Box 4, Folder 75)
    - WGH - Loyal Democrats - letters to Frank McKinney, Chairman Democratic National Committee, April 1952 (Box 4, Folder 76)
    - WGH - Rev. H.T. Neitsch re Allan Shivers, April 1952 (Box 4, Folder 77)
    - Texas Social and Legislative Conference - Lillian Collier; Margaret Reading, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 78)
    - Loyal Democrats in the Rio Grande Valley, April 1952 (Box 4, Folder 79)
    - Democrat Executive meeting - April 17-18, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 80)
    - Herman Jones re Democratic precinct chairman - Precinct 12, Travis County, March 1952 (Box 4, Folder 81)
    - State Democratic Executive Committee - Harry Seay, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 82)
    - WGH - Galveston Co. conventions, May 1952 (Box 4, Folder 83)
    - WGH - Edwin Hawes, Jr. re Wharton Co. Convention, May 1952 (Box 4, Folder 84)
    - WGH - J.H. Kavanaugh - Round Rock, Williamson Co., Texas, April 1952 (Box 4, Folder 85)
    - WGH - Jack Carter re Tarrant Co. conventions, April - May 1952 (Box 4, Folder 86)
    - WGH - Byron Skelton re Bell Co. Convention; Wright Morrow, April - May 1952 (Box 4, Folder 87)
    - Texas State Democratic Convention - San Antonio, May 27, 1952, May 1952 (Box 4, Folder 88)
    - Galveston Co. delegation to the San Antonio Convention, May 1952 (Box 4, Folder 89)
    - Platform of the Democratic Party of Texas - Loyal Democrats - S.A. May 27, 1952, May 1952 (Box 4, Folder 90)
    - San Antonio Convention minutes, May - June 1952 (Box 4, Folder 91)
    - Edwin Hawes, Jr. - Fagan Dickson - What is this Democratic Party, April 1952 (Box 4, Folder 92)
    - Statements of Allan Shivers and Fagan Dickson on the two factions of the Democratic Party, April 1952 (Box 4, Folder 93)
    - Maury Maverick to WGH re Loyal Democrats - San Antonio platform - Shivercrats, June 1952 (Box 4, Folder 94)
    - Committee on Permanent Organization - Stuart Long; WGH, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 95)
    - Kefauver for President - Ernest O. Gillam, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 96)
    - WGH - Jno. D. Mitchell re Sam Rayburn and other possible presidential candidates, March - April 1952 (Box 4, Folder 97)
    - Party loyalty pledge - instructed or uninstructed delegates, May 1952 (Box 4, Folder 98)
    - Democratic National Convention in Chicago - Maury Maverick; WGH, June 1952 (Box 4, Folder 99)
    - Democratic National Convention in Chicago, July 21, July 1952 (Box 4, Folder 100)
    - Sub-committee on Credentials - Chicago Convention, July 1952 (Box 4, Folder 101)
    - Officers and officials of the Democratic National Committee (with notes), July 1952 (Box 4, Folder 102)
    - Democratic manual for the Democratic National Convention, July 1952 (Box 4, Folder 103)
    - Texas delegates and alternates by congressional districts, Chicago Convention, July 1952 (Box 4, Folder 104)
    - Legal briefs re the two Texas delegations, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 105)
    - List of the Maverick delegation from Texas to the Chicago Convention, July 1952 (Box 4, Folder 106)
    - Democrats vs. Dixiecrats; The Texas Story, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 107)
    - WGH - Gilbert Adams re Chicago Convention and National Committee, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 108)
    - WGH to E.O. Gillam re Dixiecrats and Democrats and Chicago Convention, Sept. 8, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 109)
    - WGH letter to the Credentials Committee of the Chicago Convention, Oct. 1952 (Box 4, Folder 110)
    - Galveston Co. Democratic Executive Committee, Jan. - May 1952 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Galveston Co. Democratic Executive Committee, June - July 1952 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Galveston Co. Democratic Executive Committee, Aug. - Sept. 1952 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Election returns for the Democratic primary, July 26, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - WGH campaign for chairman of Galveston Co. Democrats, May - Aug. 1952 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Presidential campaign propaganda, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - WGH - Adlai Stevenson, Nov. 8, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Post-election Reorganizing the Democratic Party - Where do we go from here?, Nov, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - WGH - Paul W. Jeffrey re private corporation's violations of land laws, Dec. 1952 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - WGH - Maury Maverick re Stevenson - Sparkman Campaign, Oct. 1952 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Stevenson for President, Aug. - Nov. 1952 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - WGH - W.H. Kittrell re Harry Seay and Dallas/Ft. Worth politics, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - State Democratic Convention at Amarillo, Sept. 1952 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - WGH - Stuart Long - Galveston Co. and the States Democratic Convention, Aug. 4, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - State Democratic platform - adopted Sept. 9, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - WGH - E.H. Keller - Don Ellinger; John Moriarty re labor unions in politics, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - WGH - Lawrence Westbrook re real Democrats in Texas counties, Oct. 1952 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Robert E. Fitch, Intelligentsia in Defeat, The Christian Century, Nov. 26, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - WGH - Jack Haggarty - raising money for the Democratic Party, Dec. 1952 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - WGH - broadcast over KTRH radio, Dec. 1952 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - WGH to R.E. Wood, chairman of the board, Sears Roebuck and Co., on his reactionary politics, Oct. 1952 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - WGH - India Edwards re presidential election and charter for People's National Bank in Houston, Nov. - Dec. 1952 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - WGH - India Edwards re state and national Democratic Party - role of women, Aug. - Oct. 1952 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - WGH - John C. Granbery re Hall's candidates for statewide office, July 1952 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Texas Tidelands - The Truth about Tidelands, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Democratic National Convention, Aug. 1952 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Election wagers, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - WGH - Charles F. Brannan re Loyal Democrats; Chicago Convention and presidential election, June - Nov. 1952 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - WGH - George Carmack re Stevenson articles to be published in the Houston Press, Fall 1952 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Re article by LBJ for the Press, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Article by Sam Rayburn for the Houston Press, Fall 1952 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - WGH, Why Texans should vote for Stevenson, Houston Press, Sept. 25, 1952. p. 10 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Article by R.M. Boswell for the Houston Press, Fall 1952 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Re other articles for the Press, Fall 1952 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Stevenson - Sparkman campaign in the Ninth Congressional District - WGH, chairman of the Steering Committee, Oct. 1952-July 1953 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Marion Storm Memorial Committee, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - WGH - Stuart Long re Election Law, Jan. 1953 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - WGH - Fagan Dickson re politics, Jan. 1953 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Bank Closing Bill, Feb. 1953 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Letters to friends on politics, Feb. 1953 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - WGH to Bill Kittrell re Adlai Stevenson, March 1953 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - H. Bill 375, March 1953 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - WGH - Jimmy Phillips - Paul Jeffrey re Texas Business Corporation Act, March 1953 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Permanent residence status for the Alimanestiano family - Clark Thompson - Charlie Crosson, Feb. - May 1953 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - WGH - Nelson McElroy, March 1953 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - WGH - Fagan Dickson re Steven Mitchell, Mar. - Apr. 1953 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Committee for a Fair Pipeline Gas Tax, April 1953 (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - WGH - J. E. Wheat re State Democratic Executive Committee account, April 1953 (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - WGH - Fagan Dickson and Paul Holcomb re Democratic Party in Texas, April 1953 (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - WGH - India Edwards re Wright Morrow and the Chicago Convention, April 1953 (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - WGH - Drew Pearson re Sunday afternoon broadcasts, April 1953 (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - WGH - Fagan Dickson re meeting at Buchanan Dam, Apr. - May 1953 (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - WGH - Marvin Nichol re Bureau of Reclamation, May - Aug. 1953 (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - WGH - Creekmore Fath re Texas Democratic Organizing Committee, July 1953 (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - WGH - India Edwards re Democratic Digest, Aug. 1953 (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - WGH - Oveta Culp Hobby re Marine hospitals, Sept. 1953 (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - WGH - Travis Bryan re Democratic Party, Sept. 1953 (Box 5, Folder 57)
    - WGH - Creekmore Fath re Texas Democratic Party and national leadership, Sept. 1953 (Box 5, Folder 58)
    - WGH - Stuart Long re tax equalization in Galveston Co., Sept. 1953 (Box 5, Folder 59)
    - Paul Holcomb, How Texas became a No-Party State, Texas Observer, Oct. 19, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 60)
    - WGH - Boyd Taylor re Young Democratic Club of Texas, Oct. 1953 (Box 5, Folder 61)
    - WGH - Byron Skelton re Democratic Party leaders, Oct. 1953 (Box 5, Folder 62)
    - 53rd Texas Legislature, Aug. - Nov. 1953 (Box 5, Folder 63)
    - WGH - Lillian Collier re Ike and Tsanoff Address, Dec. 1953 (Box 5, Folder 64)
    - R. A. Tsanoff Intellectual Freedom, July 1953 - Sept. 1954 (Box 5, Folder 65)
    - WGH - Mrs. Joe A. Wessendorf - Stuart Long re State Board of Education, San Jacinto River Authority and the next governor, Nov. 1953 - Jan. 1954 (Box 5, Folder 66)
    - WGH - James Sewell re Democratic Advisory Council, Jan. - Dec. 1954 (Box 5, Folder 67)
    - Democratic National Committee, Feb. 1954 (Box 5, Folder 68)
    - Galveston Co. Democratic Party, Feb. - Nov. 1954 (Box 5, Folder 69)
    - WGH - Stephen A. Mitchell - Democratic Party in Texas, Jan. - June 1954 (Box 5, Folder 70)
    - Loyal Democrats - account, March 1954 (Box 5, Folder 71)
    - James Simpson - candidate for county attorney, March 1954 (Box 5, Folder 72)
    - WGH - Vic Cox - Young Democrats Club of Galveston Co., March 1954 (Box 5, Folder 73)
    - WGH - W. H. Kittrell - Horace Westwood re McCarthyism, March 1954 (Box 5, Folder 74)
    - WGH - Margaret Carter re Galveston and Tarrant Co. politics, April 1954 (Box 5, Folder 75)
    - Democratic Party conventions, April 1954 (Box 5, Folder 76)
    - Fagan Dickson - Frank E. Holman re Bricker Amendment, Jan. - May 1954 (Box 5, Folder 77)
    - WGH - Paul E. Daugherty re McCarthyism, Feb. - May 1954 (Box 5, Folder 78)
    - Galveston Co. redistricting, Aug. - Sept. 1954 (Box 5, Folder 79)
    - Marion Storm Memorial Committee, Sept. - Nov. 1954 (Box 5, Folder 80)
    - Pritchard and Abbott - Galveston Co. tax evaluation, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 81)
    - Senate Bill 186, Feb. 1955 (Box 5, Folder 82)
    - H. Bills 216 and 45, Feb. 1955 (Box 5, Folder 83)
    - H. Bill 240, Feb. 1955 (Box 5, Folder 84)
    - House Bill 662, March 1955 (Box 5, Folder 85)
    - H. Bill 588, March 1955 (Box 5, Folder 86)
    - WGH - Sen. J.M. Fulbright, July 11, 1955 (Box 5, Folder 87)
    - Galveston Co. Democratic Party, 1955 (Box 5, Folder 88)
    - One man's opinion about the problems of Texas Democrats, 1955 (Box 5, Folder 89)
    - WGH - E.L. Summers - Article on water and soil conservation for the Chronicle, Oct. 1955 (Box 5, Folder 90)
    - Democratic Advisory Council - Byron Skelton, 1955 (Box 5, Folder 91)
    - WGH - Fagan Dickson re Ike, Oct. 1955 (Box 5, Folder 92)
    - Poll tax receipts to be used in voting in 1956, Jan. 1956 (Box 5, Folder 93)
    - News coverage - Texas politics, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 94)
    - Houston Press on Allan Shivers and Tx. politics, Jan. 1956 (Box 5, Folder 95)
    - Galveston Co. Democratic Party, April 1956 (Box 5, Folder 96)
    - Texas Democratic Party - Kathleen Voigt and Byron Skelton, March - June 1956 (Box 5, Folder 97)
    - Galveston Co. conventions, May 1956 (Box 5, Folder 98)
    - State Democratic Convention - Dallas, May 1956 (Box 5, Folder 99)
    - Skelton - Randolph party, July 18, 1956, May - July 1956 (Box 5, Folder 100)
    - State Democratic Convention - Ft. Worth, Sept. 1956 (Box 5, Folder 101)
    - Oberlin mock convention, Feb. - June 1956 (Box 5, Folder 102)
    - 1956 Stevenson - Kefauver campaign, Sept. 1956 - Jan. 1957 (Box 5, Folder 103)
    - Convention votes of counties in the 17th Senatorial District, Feb. 1957 (Box 5, Folder 104)
    - WGH - Clyde Miller - WGH spoke before railway workers, March 1957 (Box 5, Folder 105)
    - Senate Bills 211 and 177, March 1957 (Box 5, Folder 106)
    - H. Bill 371, March 1957 (Box 5, Folder 107)
    - Finance Committee, Democrats of Texas, April 1957 (Box 5, Folder 108)
    - House Bill 733, April 1957 (Box 5, Folder 109)
    - Congressional record, June 1957 (Box 5, Folder 110)
    - House Bill 371 - Bob Bray, June 1957 (Box 5, Folder 111)
    - Executive Board - Democrats of Texas, July 1957 (Box 5, Folder 112)
    - Tarrant Co. - Democrats of Texas, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 113)
    - Matagorda Co. - Democrats of Texas, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 114)
    - Pritchard and Abbott, July - Dec. 1957 (Box 5, Folder 115)
    - WGH - Charles W. Britt - Brazoria Co. - Democrats of Texas, Aug. 1957 (Box 5, Folder 116)
    - WGH - Asa Willis and E.G. Power_re Hall speaking at a political rally in the Amarillo area, Sept. - Oct. 1957 (Box 5, Folder 117)
    - Senate District 17 - Galveston Co. - Democrats of Texas, Nov. 1957 (Box 5, Folder 118)
    - WGH - Paul Butler - Frankie Randolph re Hall becoming a sustaining member of the Democratic Party, Dec. 1957 (Box 5, Folder 119)
    - WGH - R.B. Tuck on the possibility of Hall running for governor, Dec. 1957 (Box 5, Folder 120)
    - Travis Co. Legislative Conference, Dec. 1957 (Box 5, Folder 121)
    - News coverage - Texas politics, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 122)
    - Hall correspondence, newsclippings, etc. re banking and bank legislation, recd., 1985-90, 5/7/91 (Box 5)
    - Taxes in Texas, Jan. - Nov. 1958 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - U.S. - House Bill 8737 - savings and loan, Jan. - April 1958 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Democrats of Texas, Jan. - Oct. 1958 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Democratic National Committee - Paul M. Butler, Byron Skelton, Jan. - Sept. 1958 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - WGH - George Nokes - Lt. governor's race, Feb. 1958 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Oil industry, March 1958 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Tidelands, March 1958 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Pritchard and Abbott, March - May 1958 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Galveston Co. Democrats - C.R. Johnson, April - Dec. 1958 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - WGH - Ronnie Dugger, April 1958 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - WGH - Hugh Wilson re high filing fees, June 1958 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - W.L. Harlan - WGH - Legislation _re credit insurance industry, June 1958 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - WGH - Everett Collier re Houston Chronicle, Oct. 1958 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - WGH - Mrs. R. D. Randolph Bill Cooper, Oct., 1958 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Halls - Willises - Texas Democrats and Republicans, Nov. 1958 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - WGH - Robert E. Hall re State Democratic Executive Committee members of the 17th District, Dec. 1958 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - News coverage - Texas politics, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Marion Storm Memorial Committee, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Lobbyist Control Act, Jan. 1959 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - WGH - Jesse Andrews - Nominating candidates for public office, Jan. 1959 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - State Democratic Executive Committee, Jan. - July 1959 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Democrats of Texas, Jan. - Sept. 1959 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Liquor laws, Feb. 1959 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - U.S. HR4245 - Larry Harlan, Feb. - March 1959 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - New tax bill for Texas - Natural Gas Tax, Feb. - April 1959 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Democratic National Committee, Feb. - Nov. 1959 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Texas HB 26, March 1959 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - WGH - Albert Peña, Jr. - Speaking in Bexar Co., March 1959 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Texas HB 732, March 1959 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Texas HB 32 - Abandoned Property Act - Ed Clark, March 1959 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Pritchard and Abbott - Galveston Co., March - Nov. 1959 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - WGH - Ronnie Dugger of the Texas Observer re Texas politics and taxes, April 1959 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Tx. House Bill 554 - Neveille Colson, April - May 1959 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - WGH - T.R. Robinson - Galveston Co. public works, May 1959 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - WGH - Frankie Randolph re Hall running for gov., May 1959 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Truman Diamond Jubilee, May 1959 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Texas House Bill 4, April 1959 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Stuart Long - Austin Report, May 1959 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Possible Democratic presidential candidates, May 1959 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Galveston Co. Democratic Party, May - Nov. 1959 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Mrs. Robt. Farmer - Gilbert Bleau - WGH re possibility of WGH running for governor, Sept. 1959 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Hospital bond issue - Galveston Co., Sept. - Nov. 1959 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - WGH - Gaston Wilder - Hall's speech in Beaumont, Sept. - Nov. 1959 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Repeal of the poll tax in Texas, Aug. - Dec. 1959 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Newsweek, Jan. 1960 (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - Repeal of the poll tax in Texas, Jan. - Dec. 1960 (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - D. O. T. clubs, Feb. - March 1960 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - WGH - W.S. Barron re W.T. McDonald, candidate for judge of the Court of Criminal Appeals, Feb. - March 1960 (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - Pritchard and Abbott, April - Sept. 1960 (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - WGH - Joseph Magliolo re candidacy of Bob Palmer, May 1960 (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - Convention - May 1960 (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - Insurance legislation, Feb. - Aug. 1960 (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - Galveston Co. Democratic Party, Sept. 1960 (Box 6, Folder 53)
    - WGH - Ronnie Dugger - Texas Observer, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 54)
    - Brazos Harbor improvements, Sept. 1960 (Box 6, Folder 55)
    - WGH - Ed Gossett re electoral reform, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 56)
    - WGH - Frank Yeager - Political appointments, Nov. 1960 (Box 6, Folder 57)
    - Church and state - Catholic influence in politics, Nov. - Dec. 1960 (Box 6, Folder 58)
    - Democracy Club of Galveston County, Dec. 1960 (Box 6, Folder 59)
    - Plans for JFK - LBJ inauguration, Dec. 1960 (Box 6, Folder 60)
    - Federal aid to education, Dec. 1960 (Box 6, Folder 61)
    - Democratic National Committee, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 62)
    - Repeal of the poll tax in Texas, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 63)
    - WGH - Ronnie Dugger - The Texas Observer, Jan. 1961 (Box 6, Folder 64)
    - Hall's possible appointment as Assistant Secretary of Interior, Feb. 1961 (Box 6, Folder 65)
    - Pritchard and Abbott, Feb. - Oct. 1961 (Box 6, Folder 66)
    - Paul Harvey - WGH re teacher pay raises, Jan. - March 1961 (Box 6, Folder 67)
    - Water Control Bill for Galveston Co., Jan. - March 1961 (Box 6, Folder 68)
    - WGH - Alex Dickey re ASC Committee, Feb. 1961 (Box 6, Folder 69)
    - State Democratic Executive Committee, Feb. 1961 (Box 6, Folder 70)
    - Tex. HB 496 and 567 re banking laws - Neil Caldwell, Feb. - March 1961 (Box 6, Folder 71)
    - Tex. HB 544 - Liquor law, March 1961 (Box 6, Folder 72)
    - Speech of Governor Nelson of Wisconsin re chamber of commerce, March 1961 (Box 6, Folder 73)
    - Tex. SB 270, March 1961 (Box 6, Folder 74)
    - Fagan Dickson - Christian cosmology and Sputnik, April - March 1961 (Box 6, Folder 75)
    - Special Senate election - Blakley vs. Tower, May 27, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 76)
    - U.S. HR 3330 and 3331, May 1961 (Box 6, Folder 77)
    - Taxes on financial institutions, July 1961 (Box 6, Folder 78)
    - Democratic coalition, Sept. 1961 (Box 6, Folder 79)
    - Galveston Co. - Politics and the Democratic Party, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 80)
    - Democratic National Committee, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 81)
    - News coverage - Democratic Party, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 82)
    - Poll tax repeal, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 83)
    - Expansion of foreign trade - WGH - Sam Low and WL Clayton, June 1962 (Box 6, Folder 84)
    - Unions and politics, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 85)
    - State's fiscal outlook for 1963-1965 - Ed Clark, Aug. 1962 (Box 6, Folder 86)
    - Pritchard and Abbott, April - Dec. 1962 (Box 6, Folder 87)
    - Texas Democratic Party, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 88)
    - Tex. Democratic Conservatives and John Connally, Oct. 1962 (Box 6, Folder 89)
    - Democratic National Committee, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 90)
    - Texas Observer - Ronnie Dugger, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 91)
    - Galveston Co. Democratic Party - C.R. Johnson, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 92)
    - Tex. Senate Bill 101, March 1962 (Box 6, Folder 93)
    - Carla Appreciation Dinner, 3/12/62, for WGH, March 1962 (Box 6, Folder 94)
    - Roster of U.S. Congressmen, Jan. 1963 (Box 6, Folder 95)
    - WGH - A.N. Slough - Texas State Industrial Union Council, Jan. 1963 (Box 6, Folder 96)
    - State Democratic Executive Committee - C.R. Johnson, Jan. - Nov. 1963 (Box 6, Folder 97)
    - Democracy Club of Galveston Co., Jan. 1963 (Box 6, Folder 98)
    - Tex. Democratic Coalition - Larry Goodwyn, Jan. - July 1963 (Box 6, Folder 99)
    - Texas S.B. 31 - Constitutional revision, April 1963 (Box 6, Folder 100)
    - Texas H.B. 492, April - May 1963 (Box 6, Folder 101)
    - Texas Senate Bill 16 - Banking legislation, April - May 1963 (Box 6, Folder 102)
    - Texas H.B. 553, May 1963 (Box 6, Folder 103)
    - Poll tax repeal, Aug. - Sept. 1963 (Box 6, Folder 104)
    - Young Democratic Clubs of Texas - Resolution honoring JFK, Sept. 1963 (Box 6, Folder 105)
    - Voters of Texas enlist - Larry Goodwyn, Aug. - Oct. 1963 (Box 6, Folder 106)
    - WGH - Neil Caldwell re J. B. Harvey and printed material for political campaigns, Oct. 1963 (Box 6, Folder 107)
    - Texas Observer - Ronnie Dugger, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 108)
    - WGH re JFK's death, Nov. - Dec. 1963 (Box 6, Folder 109)